#### Contact

9548042372 (Mobile) eddcollado@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/eddycollado-057532a8 (LinkedIn) eddy-collado.squarespace.com (Personal)

### Top Skills

Web Design Adobe Creative Suite Multiple Project Coordination

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish

# **Eddy Collado**

Certification in Full Stack Web Development at University of Denver Denver, Colorado

## Summary

Experienced Print Producer with a demonstrated history of working in the printing industry. Skilled in Web Design, Adobe Photoshop, Marketing, Social Media, and HTML/CSS. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) focused in Graphic Design from Florida State University.

## Experience

adams-mcclure Print Producer September 2018 - Present (1 year 6 months) Greater Denver Area

TerraSlate Paper & Waterproof Menus **Print Production Specialist** May 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Denver, Colorado

uBreakiFix Electronic Repair Technician October 2016 - May 2017 (8 months) Centennial, Colorado

Fixing anything with a power button.

Pop Your Pup Senior Graphic Designer October 2015 - September 2016 (1 year) Pompano, Florida

One of several artists designing digital portraits of customer submitted photos of their pet/s.

The Zimmerman Agency Creative Department Intern January 2015 - June 2015 (6 months) Produce both digital and print artwork for the following clients: Eden Roc, Cayman Islands, Casa de Campo, Cooper Tires, Pilot Pen, IronTribe, Club Med, and Time Magazine, including flash banners and hand-drawn pieces for Pilot Pen, Poster-sized ads and t-shirt designs for IronTribe Fitness, Organizing pitch presentations for Cayman Islands and Discover Florida Health, Fliers for Eden Roc and Club Med, business cards and advertisement brochures for Renaissance Aruba, hand-draw Time Magazine's Top 10 company logos from their Fortune 500 list using Pilot Pen products, and Website mockups for Eden Roc, IronTribe Fitness, Club Med, and Casa de Campo

## Education

University of Denver
Certification in Full Stack Web Development, Full Stack Web
Development · (2019 - 2020)

Florida State University
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Graphic Design · (2012 - 2014)